# Vivek

UI/ UX Developer

Phone: 9605744564, 7012727810

Email: vivekv1122@gmail.com

My Portfolio: https://vivekvhere.github.io/



### **ABOUT**

I'm a Front end UI/UX Developer with an experience of 4 years. My Mind is a balanced blend of creative and analytical qualities, making for a pretty cool skill set! I crave order, love all things design, and seek harmony between work/life. I'm always on the lookout for exciting projects to work on.

## **RESPONSIBILITIES**

- Estimating the time span for a project based on client requirements.
- Managing and delivering the solution in a time-bound manner
- Understanding the problem, designing and developing a solution.
- Managing and delivering the solution in a time-bound manner.
- Documents and demonstrates solutions by developing documentation code comments and clear code.
- Assists in system specification design and solution deployment.
- Coordinating with the QA department for issue resolution.

## **SKILLS**

Skill	Experience
HTML	EXPERTIZED
CSS,CSS3	EXPERTIZED
SASS	EXPERTIZED
Bootstrap 4	EXPERTIZED
JavaScript	EXPERTIZED

Angular JS	GOOD
jQuery	EXPERTIZED
Git	EXPERTIZED
React JS	GOOD

#### **EXPERIENCE**

• SAYONE TECHNOLOGIES PVT LTD, KOCHI KERALA — UI/UX DEVELOPER.

Feb 2019 - Present

• COMCUBE INTEGRATED SOLUTIONS PVT LTD— UI/UX DEVELOPER.

Jan 2017 - Jan 2019

#### **EDUCATION**

## MCA

ICET, Muvattupuzha

Jun 2014 - Dec 2016

BCA

Nirmala College, Muvattupuzha Jun 2011 - Mar 2014

#### **OTHER SKILLS**

- Leadership quality including coordinating, organizing, guiding, and supporting.
- Proactive & Positive
- Smart working than Hard Working
- Dedicated, Flexible, and Quick/Self Learner

## **PROJECTS**

Projects	Role	Tools	Comments
Winebiz	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 100% frontend part. Also got client appreciation for this project
IPC	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 80% work in IPC after joining sayone. Notable work - ID CARD printing.
Newsly	UI DEVELOPER	AMP,HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 100% frontend part. Learned new technology called "AMP" and implemented succssfully.
FMFB	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 60% work in this project after joining sayone.
Datafloq	UI DEVELOPER	AMP,HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 60% work in this project after joining sayone.
Etailpet	UI DEVELOPER	SASS,HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 20% work in this project after joining sayone.
Sayone LMS	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 100% frontend part.
Beco LMS	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 90% frontend part.
Skillconnect 360	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3,	Handled 100% frontend

		BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	part.
Paigo app	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 100% frontend part.
Sayone website rewamp	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 50% frontend part.
Planbaker	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 20% work in this project after joining sayone.
HMS- Hospital management system	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Worked on landing page design for dashboard and handed over to client
Position 2	UI DEVELOPER	REACT,HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Dedicated mode: Successfuly completed assigned tasks in given time frame.
Goshop7	UI DEVELOPER	HTML, CSS3, BOOTRAP4, JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT	Handled 50% frontend part.

## **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that all the details furnished above are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

- VIVEK